Now we start to make a round-shaped pillow
Create a diameter of 230mm
Then engrave a layer and turn it over to add pressure
Have a look at the result
Put a piece of new fabric on the round-shaped sheet
Cut the end of the thread
Reduce the strength of the sand and reduce the strength of the corner line to 1, and the board will expand into a ball through pressure.
If the strength of the corner line is increased a little, the ball will be a little flat.
When the strength of the corner line is reduced to 0, the board will become completely round, like a ball.
Continue to carve a layer to make the color of the outside of the abacus.
Change the sewing line between the boards to Custom Angle, so that the boards can be sewn together without leaving any gaps.
Then cancel the connection between the boards of the abacus, because it will adjust the size of the outer board later.
Now there is still a gap between the boards, because the sewing line between the boards has not been changed to Custom Angle.
Reduce the strength of the two-layer board to 10 or 8, otherwise the fabric wrinkles will not appear.
Apply a new fabric to the outer layer.
Change the sewing line between the boards to 5 or 6, and the board will become completely round.
Then cancel the connection between the boards.
Increase the strength of the corner line of the outer board to 5, so that the border will also wrinkle a little.
Then turn it over and press it up.
Then reduce the particle diameter to 5, so that the fold is more detailed
If you think there are not enough folds around the sewing line, you can use the ruler tool to increase the shrinkage to 3
Create along the outer line
Finally, the seam line has a circle of folds
contribution beam
The board about the creation has a smaller circle of fold around, but the goal is a circle that is defined
If you want to use a T-shaped fold that has more depth, you can add a felt to help bounce the sewing line
Chatipare sewing line tool will create a circle around the line
You can also use the line-cut line function, but the line-cut line function will randomly open and extend, which will lead to the line-cut line extending along the curve to the outside of the board.
You can use the edit line function to select the excess lines and delete them.
Then drag a point of the line to the starting position to complete the edit.
This video ends here. See you in the next video.